Ha ha ha
Pouring
Pouring out the car
Ha ha ha ha ha ha
Nick
And what that leaves after ninety days
Hey
I was invisible cool
I don't feel so good
You can keep it pee
Okay
Best stand on that all the on the globe
And we put the the only thing to stop the beat
Look at my son
Pride is not the word
I'm looking for
Hey
How's it going
So beautiful
Hello to the camera
Hello camera
All right now
Start running
U u
U
I'm poopies
And this is the hundred mile an hour slip and slide
Ha ha ha ha
Love you all
I do me
No matter what i do on my way
You wait a minute
No
Oh my god
Holy  man
Oh
Oh my god
It's so big
It's so
You feel you
Bad boys
What you gonna do
Or what you gonna do when they come for you
Bad boys
What you gonna do
What you gonna do when they come for you
In this is that in adi
I will tame the rock
Rock your hips
I'm having cash
I can take your beat it up
Like this
Put it on fresh fit
Like
I think i don't like this soon
I can't believe i let you get away
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I think i'd be strong
I want you back up right to do
You think i'm a brother
Don't wanna let you go
Baby
Cause i know it's
You are my special
Looking out to it again
What the
Oh
My god
Oh no
I'm not the hero the worldwide
And i not the hero the world needs
But i am the hero that the world gets
Me which problem
Let me take me
Yeah
It's the secret brother
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you happy birthday
Happy birthday
Happy
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Oh yeah
Good good
Got the girl or the god was the heavy
A good skin
Nice part to
I'm not the hero the worldwide
And i not the hero the world needs
But i am the hero that the world gets
I know
You
Haha
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Show me your bad dog
I don't want to see any of these
Like good boys and good girls sitting for a cookie
Show me that bad dog
I want the one who sits on the fifty
Th try
I want the dog
That's
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
You ready
Bro yeah
Bro
This is so tardy
Oh no
Do you have
You never get it open
I am not the same baby
I don't know why
I just need a good fight
I don't have
You know
Cause i wanna make it
Du du
Du
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I don't know
But i don't know that
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I was just a great
Oh
My god
I finally got inside
I see your face
And it's nothing like i've ever known before love is in open
Ha ha ha ha
Yo yo yo yo a detroit casino beats a battle to no o o o o
Who left you over
It was salman
Oh yeah
But
My brain
Oh
My god
Hey
Yeah
That's mine
No
Okay
Go no
That's mine
That's my bag
No no
Go go go
That's mine
As long as you don't grab my wallet and stuff
Oh my god
All my stuff go
That's my
That's that's go no go get
That's my dad
Go
No no
You guys
My my camera's so expensive
He's trying to go
This one as the sports of what
As my witness
Oh that more job
But the other interior creative camera
How the this is
This is the place
What's that
Dj's passed out in the art barbie's on the barbecue
This hickey arrows pictures of last night and
Out blood
But pretty sure it
Oh damn last friday
Then they contract on three one
Two three one
A fire on friday night
We were shaking in the park
Skinny
Dipping in the dark
And had all the magic while on the outside
Yeah
I think we both love
Always
We see
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Oh ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Trust no one
Trust
First one you waiting
I got real love baby
Until you taste me
I won't be in love
Yes
Let's go
Thank you
Yes
Let's go
You make your way
Have you
Ah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha